CURRICULUM VITAE



CONTACT

- \$ 9881136862
- admuthevaishali@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/vaishaliadmuthe-2820a3b8
- Flat No. C 17, RPratibha esidency, Sasanenagar, Hadapsar, Pune:411028

EDUCATION

IIM EXECUTIVE CERTIFICATE PROGRAMME IN STRATEGIC MARKETING MANAGEMENT IIM Kashipur

BATCHOLER OF ARTS Shivaji University Kolhapur

ADVANCE COMPUTER DIPLOMA IN OFFICE AUTOMATION
CDAC Pune

ADVANCE DIPLOMA IN FASHION DESIGNING India International Trade Centre (IITC)

SKILLS

Strategy Planning

Leadership

Consultative Counseling

Effective Communication

Active Listening

Convincing

VAISHALI ADMUTHE

Sales and Marketing Professional

PROFILE

A strong and focused sales and marketing professional with experience in B2B and B2C sales. More than 8 years' experience in education sales and marketing. Experienced in leadling team of up-to 60. Work towards the professional goals with never give-up attitude

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRANCHISEE MANAGER GURU EDUCATION INDIA PVT LTD

01/2023 - 04/2023

Franchisee sales and setup and after sales service management, B2 B Segment, Done 11 Franchisee setups in 2.5 months

ASISTANT SALES MANAGER

AMIGO ACADEMY PVT LTD

05/2022 - 12/2022

Arranging and conducting seminars at colleges, Generating leads, Counseling and Converting in actual Admissions. Documentation, Loan process for loan students, B2B and B2C both segments. Handling branch operations

BRANCH MANAGER

HELP OVERSEAS IMMIGRATIONS PVT LTD 03/2022 - 05/2022

Handled 60 people team. Worked for visa process for India and South African countries, Visa process, Documentation, Application and Stamping and other formalities related guidance, Payment getaway's and secure payment options suggestions, payment recovery.

SALES MANAGER

KATHARIZO INDIA PVT LTD

09/2021 - 02/2022

Sales and Marketing Manager of the company. B2B, B2C, Conducting Brand awareness activities, Events, Sponsoring events, B2B meetings and Tieups, Preparing and signing agreements. Increased Sales by 40%. Sales team recruitment, Review meetings, planning strategies and setting sales targets, creating roadmaps, Reporting to the Director and CEO.

ADMISSION COUNSELOR

ORCHIDS INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL (K12 TECHNO SERVICES)

12/2019 - 8/2021

Counseling parents on location, through virtual meetings, through phone calls and converting into admissions. Giving school tours, Making them understand 21st century education requirements and advance facilities provided by the school. The only counselor retained and promoted in lockdown period. Handled 6 branches single handedly. Lead 20 PRO's team.

COMPUTER SKILLS

MS Office Advance Excel Adobe Illustrator Internet Research

INTERESTS

Learning New Skills

Reading Books

Listening Podcasts

Listening to music

MY BELIEFS

Everything is possible if you work towards it, Never give up. Give your everything to what you want to achieve, Limitations most of the time are only our own thoughts.

MY PASSION

MY WORK

PRE/ADMIN/ADMISSION COUNSELOR

OXFORD WORLD SCHOOL

08/2018 - 10/2019

Worked as a contact point for the school as a Public Relation Executive. Connecting Preschool heads, Setting meetings and preparing LOU. Counseling Walk-in parents and converting in admissions. Taking followups for admission and documentation, Making sure every document is at place and safe. Handling day to day admin tasks, reporting, Inventory management, Library Management.

HEAD OF THE DEPARTMENT FASHION DESIGNING

BAHINABAI CHOUDHARY CHARITABLE TRUST 04/2011-05/2015

Handling all activities of the department, Creating brand awareness, arranging and conducting seminars, Generating leads, Counseling and converting into admissions. Planning curriculum as per industry standards, Designing Logo and Pamphlets. Interviewing and hiring the staff.



PERSONAL PROJECTS

HOME BASED FASHION DESIGNING BOUTIQUE

2007-05/2017

Custom designing Clothing and selling to the niche market Designing clothing for women as per occasion. Fabric and raw material Sourcing.

Creating new trends, generating new market, arranging promotional activities, Generating new customer base, upselling etc.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Only counselor retained, promoted and got salary hike in lockdown by Orchids The International School

Done 8 admissions from a seminar in a single day

DELARETION

Hereby I declare that all above provided information is 100% true.



Place:



Date:



Signature: